<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Knife Sharpening Services on On Point Cutlery - Traverse City Knife Sharpening &amp; Mobile Knife Sharpening</title>
    <link>https://onpointcutlery.com/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Knife Sharpening Services on On Point Cutlery - Traverse City Knife Sharpening &amp; Mobile Knife Sharpening</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://onpointcutlery.com/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Traverse City Commercial Knife Sharpening</title>
      <link>https://onpointcutlery.com/services/commercial-knife-sharpening-traverse-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://onpointcutlery.com/services/commercial-knife-sharpening-traverse-city/</guid>
      <description>We offer a variety of commercial knife services. Whether you want your kitchen&amp;rsquo;s knives sharpened or want to scale your business by investing in a commercial knife exchange program, we have you covered. We come to you and handle gathering, sharpening, and replacing your knives. In addition to knives, we sharpen many other tools and blades. Take a look at our commercial services to see if we can help improve your experience with freshly honed edges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Free Knife Sharpening</title>
      <link>https://onpointcutlery.com/services/contact-free-knife-sharpening/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://onpointcutlery.com/services/contact-free-knife-sharpening/</guid>
      <description>We care about the health and safety of Northern Michigan. That is why we make sure to practice all local mandates regarding covid-19 safety measures. We will update this page as needed as new information comes available to keeping your cutley and tool maintenance as safe as possible.
Covid-19 Notice For Restaurants &amp;amp; Commercial Kitchens Our services take safety and sanitzation into account. If you are a commercial kitchen customer we prioritize your safety.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garden Tools Sharpening</title>
      <link>https://onpointcutlery.com/services/garden-tool-sharpening-traverse-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://onpointcutlery.com/services/garden-tool-sharpening-traverse-city/</guid>
      <description>Is your hand tiller putting a damper on your gardening hobby? Maybe your weeding sickle is not removing weeds as efficiently anymore? Cutting or pruning with dull blades often results in damaged branches. The rips, tears, and lacerations that this cause can make your garden susceptible to disease.
Garden Tools Sharpening And Care  Rinse your digging tools with a garden hose and use a wire brush to clean the dirt of of them prior to storage Give your pruners, loopers, and shearers a quick scrub with warm soapy water If your garden tools are exposed to diseased plants or infested soils, give them a quick wash in bleach-diluted water to kill any bacteria Avoid using petroleum products on your hand tools to not introduce contamination into the soil Keep disinfecting wipes handy to remove any sap, bacteria, or fungus from your hands and tools for a quick clean up Store tools in a dry, well ventilated area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Knife Sharpening</title>
      <link>https://onpointcutlery.com/services/mobile-knife-sharpening/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://onpointcutlery.com/services/mobile-knife-sharpening/</guid>
      <description>Our highly skilled sharpening technicials will come to your home or business and sharpen on premise. We offer non-contractual services for your home or commercial kitchen. Our mobile sharpening workstation is fully equipped to sharpen most common commercial and residential tools. Have an uncommon tool? Just ask! The principles of blade sharpening hold true across many tools and we are glad to assess your needs and help you get a sharper edge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Woodworking Tools</title>
      <link>https://onpointcutlery.com/services/woodworking-tool-sharpening-traverse-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://onpointcutlery.com/services/woodworking-tool-sharpening-traverse-city/</guid>
      <description>Sharpening is a skill achieved through repetition and practice. Sharp woodworking tools is a necessity and not a luxury. We sharpen all types of woodworking tools so that you don&amp;rsquo;t have to. If you are not comfortable with restoring your edge then leave it to us! We are happy to restore your tired woodworking tools. Get back to your joinery, carving, and carpentry jobs today. Contact us to discuss which woodworking tools you need sharpened.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Commercial Knife Swap Program</title>
      <link>https://onpointcutlery.com/services/commercial-knife-swap-out-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://onpointcutlery.com/services/commercial-knife-swap-out-program/</guid>
      <description>On Point Cutlery knife sharpening service and exchange program is designed for commercial kitchens, restaurants, and supermarkets. Running your business can be even easier with our straight forward knife exchange program. Sharp knives and sharp blades will be delivered to you on a regular schedule.
Traverse City Commercial Knife Exchange  We will assist you in creating a cutlery service program that is customized for the needs of your kitcken While one set of knifes is in use at your kitchen, another set is at our service center being sharpened and repaired.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Residential Knife Sharpening</title>
      <link>https://onpointcutlery.com/services/residential-knife-sharpening-traverse-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://onpointcutlery.com/services/residential-knife-sharpening-traverse-city/</guid>
      <description>Being a home cook, private chef, or aspiring Chopped contestant, you understand the value of sharp knives. Maybe you have an old trowel that you just love or a shovel that isn&amp;rsquo;t performing. We look forward to coming to your home and sharpening your tools on premise. No need to gather all of your tools and transport them to a shop. Let us come and conveniently sharpen your knives.
Northern Michigan Residential Knife Sharpening We come to your home in Northern Michigan and sharpen your knives and tools.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
